nibbledish.com 2017-10-31

# Chicken Recipes, Crock Pot Recipes, Chili Recipe & more @ Nibbledish!

This Privacy Policy describes the manner in which NibbleDish.com collects information from you and how we use and maintain that information.

**Information we collect**

  * **Personal identification information.**   We only collect personal identification information provided by you when you register on the site as a user on our site or subscribe to a newsletter. The information collected may include your name and email address as applicable.  You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. You can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain site related activities.
  * **Non-personal identification information**. We may collect non-personal identification information about you when you visit and interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include browser information, device information (such as hardware model and operating system), log information (such as details of how you used the site and IP address), cookies and anonymous identifiers.

**Web browser cookies**

Cookies are small files that are transferred to your computer through your web browser when you visit a site that enables the site to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can choose to set your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the site may not function properly without cookies.

We may use cookies to save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertising data and compile data about site traffic and interaction to provide a better site experience.

**How we use collected information**

We may use personal information collected for the following purposes:

  * **To personalize your experience.  **We may use information collected to understand how you individually or collectively with other users make use of our site.
  * **To improve our Site.   **We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * **To send periodic emails.   **The email address you provide when contacting us through our site will be used to respond to your inquiries. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you may receive emails that include company news, content updates and related product or service information. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**Opt-out and unsubscribe policy**

You have the option not to register any personal information with us to opt out of subscribing to newsletters.  You can also opt not to participate in certain interactive areas of the site, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from you.

As explained above, we may use personal information collected to send periodic emails and may share or sell this information to third parties.  If at any time you with to discontinue from receiving future email communications from us, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions included at the bottom of each email or you may contact through our site or email us at [info@nibbledish.com](mailto:info@nibbledish.com)

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information.  While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-parties from illegally obtaining this information.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website or administrating activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys.

We may also release your personal identifiable information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided in aggregate to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party websites**

You may find advertising or other content on our site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by sites linked to or from our site. Browsing and interaction on any other site, including sites which have a link to our site, is subject to that site's own privacy policy and terms of use.

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to you by advertising partners, who may send their own unique cookies through your browser. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Compliance with Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

The safety and privacy of children is important to us.  We do not knowingly collect or maintain information from users who are under the age of 13.  Our site is directed at a general audience and intended to be used by adults.  No part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Companies that collect personally identifiable information from California residents and disclose such information to third parties (including affiliated entities) for marketing purposes must, in response to a request by a consumer, either (1) provide a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or (2) provide a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties. We have elected the second option and you may request that your personal information not be shared with third parties by contacting us as described in our opt-out and unsubscribe policy above.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and change last modified date indicated at the bottom of this page.  If the changes are significant we will provide a more prominent notice.  We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

**Consent**

By accessing and using this site you signify your acceptance of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.  If any changes to this policy are unacceptable to you, you must discontinue using the site.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

http://nibbledish.com/contact

or

Last modified:  July 18, 2012
